One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
Navy HQ
New World
What?!
The world’s going to
sink into the sea?!
What are you even
talking about, Dr. Vegapunk?!
Mock
Town,
Town of Ridicule
This guy’s a riot!
Takin’ advantage of his own death,
usin’ it to try to cause mayhem in the world!
How’s it even possible
for the whole world to go under?!
If you’re gonna lie,
at least make it believable!
City of
Water
Water Seven
I’d believe him if he was only talking about our country,
where the land’s been sinking in deeper every year...
But the whole damn world?
It’s not just a matter of
high tide and low tide, is it?
Impel Down,
the Under-
water
Prison
Man, don’t you just love this?
If Impel Down floods,
what’re you gonna do about it?
It’s your job to
keep the prisoners safe, isn’t it,
Magellan?
Indeed,
the whole place went into panic
when the sea level rose by a meter the other day.
How many meters will it be,
should the entire world go under?
A five-meter rise
would destroy most cities.
Think we oughta move?
To much higher ground?!
Ryugu Kingdom
Fishman Island
Father...
What do you think will happen?
It baffles the mind, jamon.
What is he saying?!
Future Island
Egghead
He’s the world’s greatest scientist!
He can wreak havoc on the world,
even with a lie!
It’s total nonsense!
The Wings of Icarus
Dr. Vegapunk!
Destroy the Transmission Transponder Snail!
No, destroy all life forms
you can hear!
All other concerns are secondary!
Come on!
Just how much’re you
gonna give away?!
Stella!
This will be a bit in the future
from where I’m standing,
but mere days
after I make this recording,
assuming the sensor I created
and my calculations are right,
an unusual earthquake
will shake the entire world.
Uh?
Is that about today’s earthquake?!
But Vegapunk’s
supposed to be dead by now!
Then...
Then as a result, the sea levels will rise
by approximately one meter around the world,
and some islands are certain
to become uninhabitable!
Eh? Is this a prophecy?
As such, the loss of numerous beaches
around the world would be inevitable.
If this turns out to be incorrect,
feel free to ignore
everything else I tell you.
How?! This is creepy, man!
He got it all right!
But if it does happen,
pay very close attention
to what I’m about to say!
That earthquake is the furthest possible thing
from a natural phenomenon!
Vegapunk!
You will not speak another word!
Zeus!
Aubade Coup Droit!
Bubble Gun!
Just go away!
I...
I, in my own humble way...
...wished for peace...
You damned insects!
Cien Fleurs:
Spider Net!
Get out of my way!
Huh?
Mars, have you checked
the power plant?
Not yet.
That room, more so than any others,
must remain intact.
I will go!
Yes... I wished for peace
in my own humble way...
But that was...
...my first crime.
I dreamed of unlimited energy...
Driven by...
Driven by a desire
to bring major progress to the world...
The Mother Flame!
Mother Flame
I flew...
...too close to the sun.
This is not it, either!
Slaughter every living thing in the lab!
I’m going to explain, in order,
the events about
to take place in our world.
No luck! Not even a dent!
What is that thing?
It’s not even flinching!
Hotowowowow!
Hey! You’re gonna be burned to a crisp!
Get moving!
This is about the century
roughly between 900 to 800 years ago.
There is a void in history
around that period of time.
Hey, Marines! What are you even doing-eh?!
Shut him up already!
It is referred to as the Void Century,
and it has been erased from history.
The death penalty is not enough!
Present his corpse! I’ll chop it into pieces!
The Void Century?
I must say, what might that be?
The only way to learn about
that period of time...
...is to decipher the letters from the past
called Poneglyphs...
...which are scattered
all over the world.
Orange
Town,
East
Blue
Well, long, long ago
WORLD
There were 20 kings who got together
and they created the world!
Doesn’t that old guy know that?
What do you think, Chouchou?
Deciphering Poneglyphs is strictly prohibited
by the World Government,
but despite being a Government scientist,
I tried my hand at it.
That’s my...
...second crime.
I studied books that some brilliant archaeologists
preserved through sheer tenacity,
deciphered a number of Poneglyphs,
and pushed the research
as far as I could.
I bear not even the slightest regret!
History, you see, tells a story!
But all I have learned...
...is an incomplete story of that century.
Filling in the gaps with my own speculations
would be inappropriate,
so I’ll pass on to you
only the facts I’m sure of.
Hey! Don’t even bother tryin’, Straw Hat!
The protagonist of this story...
...is a man, born 900 years ago
in an impossibly advanced kingdom.
This oughta do it!
Like the Sun God Nika
spoken of in the Elbaph legend...
...he fought with a stretchy, elastic body.
His name was Joyboy.
Ow, ow, hothothot...!
Ooh, yow, ow, hooot...!
Stop tryin’ to make us laugh!
You never learn!
It burrrrns!
He was the very first man
in this world of the sea...
...to be called a pirate.
Flower Capital
Land of Wano
Joyboy...
Why was he called a pirate?
Hmm... It is surprising that external signals
are being received within this country.
Orochi had it at the castle,
and it really came in handy!
So Joyboy was a pirate...
He sounds just like Luffy.
Do you know of Joyboy, my Lord?
Big Bro Luffy...
I wanna see him again soon!
Aye, me too.
Naval Branch G-4
Prison
Joyboy?
Is he stronger than our captain?
No way, right? Captain Kid.
Go easy on him...
He’s already dead.
Former Fake Luffy
Demalo Black
That’s our Big Boss Kid!
You gots a big heart.
So handsome!
Of course he was weaker than me!
Joyball!
Uh... I think it’s “boy”.
Joy... boy?
I’ve only read a handful of Poneglyphs,
but what was inscribed on them
was a record of a great war.
Joyboy fought against
the World Government of today.
Huh? Does he mean us?
Well, if he was a pirate...
Vegapunk!
To be more precise, it was
the precursor of the World Government,
the temporary coalition
consisting of twenty kingdoms,
known as the Alliance!
It could be argued that Joyboy’s faction
was so strong that it compelled them to join forces.
Without knowing the spark that caused the war,
I’ll call it a clash of ideologies,
rather than a matter of good and evil.
Zou,
New
World
As I mentioned earlier,
the country of Joyboy’s birth...
...had a civilization unbelievably
advanced for its time 900 years ago.
Joyboy...
I wonder if he had some
connection with Zunesha.
The weapons that existed
during that century-long war...
...were apparently beyond the capacity of
modern science to create.
That’s amazing!
What’re you going on about,
you peanutty idiot!
Oh, no!
Boss, forget that nonsense. I’m hungry!
Nonsense?!
Not even a genius like me
could replicate them!
That’s not something to brag about,
you moron!
Yes...
That’s where...
...the problem lies.
Zoro-san! Jinbe-san!
Ow, ow, ow...
Wait a minute!
It’s moving!
Look! Aren’t the clouds stretching?!
They are!
But why are they?
Is this what Edison-san meant when he said
he’d help us land on the water safely?
Ah!
You’re right! If the clouds stretch out,
we can reach the sea!
Now we can make our getaway!
Yes!
Yay!
Edison...
Y’all gotta get outta here
no matter what, Straw Hats!
Dun let da World Government...
...catch y’all!
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru